oshkosh.com 2017-03-20

# Carters.com | OshKoshBgosh.com Privacy Policy

## 

### Our Privacy Policy

_Last updated: October 20, 2011_

#### Our Commitment

We respect your privacy and understand the importance of protecting your personal information, and we stand behind the generations of trust that our customers have placed in the Carter’s and OshKosh B’gosh brands. Maintaining your privacy and trust is very important to us. Please contact our Consumer Affairs team at 888-782-9548 if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy.

#### Our Policy

This policy applies to information collected by our Carter’s and OshKosh B’gosh retail stores, as well as by our websites, including [www.Carters.com ](http://www.carters.com/)and [www.OshKoshBgosh.com](http://www.oshkoshbgosh.com/) (collectively, the “websites”). The questions and answers below cover the type of information we collect from you, how we protect your information, how we use your information, and what choices you have about how we use your information.

We reserve the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time, so we encourage you to check back periodically so that you are always aware of our most current policies regarding your privacy. The policy date above will change on the date any policy changes are made.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact Consumer Affairs at 888-782-9548, [send us an email](mailto:contactus@carters.com), or drop us a note by mail at _Carter’s Consumer Affairs, 206 State Street, Oshkosh, WI 54901._

_Personally Identifiable Information_

We may collect personally identifiable information from you, such as your name, email address, physical address, phone number, credit card number, gender, birthday, your children’s names, and your children’s gender when you order products through one of our websites or by phone; purchase our products in our stores; save your information with us online; sign up to receive promotional materials over email or in the mail; or participate in a contest, promotion or survey. Some of the personally identifiable information we collect from you, such as your name, address, phone number, email address, and credit card information, is required in order to process your online order, respond to your requests, and contact you about your order, if necessary. Other information we may request is optional information, which you may choose not to provide, but which helps us make relevant suggestions and offers to you based on your shopping history, children’s ages, etc.

_Non-Personally Identifiable Information_

We also collect non-personally identifiable information that enables us to enhance your shopping experience by tailoring information to fit your personal taste and interests, such as the information about your product interests and purchases. Examples of non-personally identifiable information include the date and time of your visit, the originating IP address, the pages and images requested, and your purchases.

_Cookies_

Like most websites, we may place cookies on your computer to collect information about how you use our websites. The information that we collect about you through cookies is not personally identifiable. A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies for a variety of purposes, such as to improve the quality of our services and the design and content of our websites; to track user trends; to enable us to provide a more personalized experience when you browse our websites; and keep you up to date on products, promotions, and other email communications that may be of interest. We may also use technologies such as our own cookies to provide you with personalized online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of this advertising, click here. Cookies may help us collect information about the browser types, pages visited, purchases made, date and time of your visit, and other click-stream data. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to be alerted when a cookie is being sent. However, some of our features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

We also use third party providers to help us collect and analyze information on our websites and to measure the effectiveness of information displayed on our websites. Such service providers may place cookies on your computer on our behalf when you access our websites. For example, we work with Coremetrics to help us understand how users interact with our websites. Coremetrics will place cookies on your computer to collect information on our behalf, including information about which search engine referred you, which items you placed in shopping carts, which items you abandoned, and what purchases you made. Coremetrics then analyzes the information it collects from our websites, and reports back to us. We use the information to help us understand your interests and how to better serve you. It also helps us provide you with more personalized product offerings. You may choose to opt out of Coremetrics' collection and analysis of your browsing and purchasing data. You may also choose to continue to benefit from the improved shopping experience that Coremetrics’ analysis allows us to provide, but maintain your anonymity. Learn more about Coremetrics [See Coremetrics Opt Out implementation instructions] and the various levels of privacy and confidentiality you can select with respect to Coremetrics’ services, as well as how to exercise your opt out choices.

To learn more, or to opt-out of receiving advertisements tailored to your interests by our third party partners, visit the Network Advertising Initiative at www.networkadvertising.org/choices.

We may use information you provide to us for a variety of purposes, including to process and fulfill your transactions, such as purchases, refunds and exchanges; to contact you about new products, services, special events and promotions, unless you have opted out as described below; to conduct contests, sweepstakes and promotions, if you signed up to participate; to help us learn about your shopping preferences; to help us improve our websites, stores, products and services; and to enhance your shopping experience. We may combine any information collected about you in stores with that collected through our websites in order to enhance and personalize your shopping experience, and for promotional purposes.

All personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information we collect about you may be shared with our affiliates and subsidiaries. We may also share personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information about you with unaffiliated third parties for purposes of providing services to us. When you complete a purchase, we may share information about you and your purchase with other companies for the purpose of processing your transaction, including credit card authorization, and order processing and fulfillment. We may share your information with our other service providers who collect, manage and analyze our customer information on our behalf and perform services on our behalf, such as sending promotions and other communications and conducting contests and surveys.

We may also share your information with third parties when we believe such disclosure is required to (i) comply with laws, regulations and/or government policies; (ii) comply with court orders, legal processes, or government enforcement actions; (iii) establish or exercise our legal rights, protect our rights and interests, or defend against legal claims; or (iv) detect, investigate, prevent, or take action with respect to illegal activities, suspected fraud or misconduct, securities or technical issues, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations of our Terms of Use or our Privacy Policy.

We may provide your information to carefully selected unaffiliated companies when we believe their products or services may be of interest to you or to other merchants and merchant exchanges who may, in turn, use such information for marketing purposes.

If for any reason you do not wish us to share your information with unaffiliated third parties who use it for marketing purposes, please either inform our Consumer Affairs team at 888-782-9548, [send us an email](mailto:contactus@carters.com), or send us a note at _Carter’s Consumer Affairs, 206 State Street, Oshkosh, WI 54901._

In the event we, or any of our affiliates or subsidiaries, are involved in a business transaction such as a merger, an acquisition, or any form of sale of all or a portion of our stock or assets, we may transfer your personal information to the buyer, and your personal information may become subject to a different privacy policy.

##### Do we collect information from children under the age of 13?

Back to the Top

No. Protecting children’s privacy is extremely important to us. Our websites are not directed to children under 13 years of age, and we do not intentionally collect or maintain any personal information from children under the age of 13.

##### Is my personally identifiable information collected and maintained in the United States?

Back to the Top

Yes. We are a U.S. company and your personally identifiable information submitted by you through our websites is collected and maintained in the United States, regardless of the geographic location or country where the information originated. If you do not consent to your personally identifiable information being collected and maintained in the United States, then you should not enter such information through our websites.

We love to hear about all of your family’s big and little changes! Is your family growing, or have you moved? Simply [sign in to your account](https://www.oshkosh.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-Carters-Site/default/Account-StartRegister) at www.Carters.com or www.OshKoshBgosh.com to change your personal information in your account profile at any time.

You can also ask us to update your information by contacting us at 888-782-9548, sending us an email, or dropping us a note at _Carter’s Consumer Affairs, 206 State Street, Oshkosh, WI 54901._ Please note that any request to update your information may take up to 10 business days to process.

If you decide you do not want to receive promotional materials from us, such as materials about our special offers and events, you can do so by [updating your account](https://www.oshkosh.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-Carters-Site/default/Account-StartRegister) at Carters.com or OshKoshBgosh.com, to change your preferences. You can also do so by contacting us by phone 888-782-9548, sending us an email, or dropping us a note at _Carter’s Consumer Affairs, 206 State Street, Oshkosh, WI 54901._ You can also unsubscribe from receiving any future emails from us by clicking “unsubscribe” on any emails you receive from us.

Your patience is appreciated as it takes approximately 10 business days to remove your name from our email list and approximately 8 – 10 weeks to remove your name from our mailing list. 

We take a number of precautions to provide a secure shopping environment. We implement many layers of safeguards to protect your safety and privacy. These include electronic safeguards like Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) when you transmit information to our sites, among other physical and contractual practices and policies.

If you prefer, you may always place your order by telephone at 877-333-0117 from [8am-12am EST] daily (except holidays).

Please be aware that our websites may contain links to other websites hosted by third parties. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the content or privacy practices and policies of such third party websites. This Privacy Policy does not describe the information collection and disclosure practices of such third parties. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of such third party websites.

Under California law, as a California resident you have the right to request from us the names and addresses of third parties to whom we disclosed personal information about you in the preceding calendar year and whom we know or reasonably should know to have used such information for direct marketing purposes. To request the above information, please contact us at 888-782-9548, or write to us at _Carter’s Consumer Affairs, 206 State Street, Oshkosh, WI 54901._ Please note that we are only required to respond to your request once during the course of any calendar year.

We are very sensitive to your privacy concerns. If you have any questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact Consumer Affairs at 888-782-9548, [send us an email](mailto:contactus@carters.com), or drop us a note at _Carter’s Consumer Affairs, 206 State Street, Oshkosh, WI 54901._

Our Coremetrics site usage statistics system allows you to view or change your profile. There are 3 different levels of data collection:

#### Change your current opt-out option:

    * Click for Anonymous Opt-Out. This setting allows Coremetrics to anonymously capture the visitor's Web actions (including the data collected in Coremetrics reporting). All actions are grouped with all other anonymous visitors.
    * Click for Total Opt-Out. The data is not collected by Coremetrics' data collection front-end servers and, consequently, is not included in Coremetrics reporting.
    * Click to opt-in. This setting will again allow Coremetrics to capture all Web actions and includes the data collected in Coremetrics reporting.
    * View Current Coremetrics Opt-out Status.
